<resources>
    <string name="app_name">VVUSA</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="next">NEXT</string>
    <string name="skip">SKIP</string>
    <string name="start">GOT IT</string>

    <string name="slide_1_title">Hostel management</string>
    <string name="slide_1_desc">Managing hostels on campus has become a lot more easier with few simple taps.</string>

    <string name="slide_2_title">Cafeteria management</string>
    <string name="slide_2_desc">Getting your food at the Cafeteria has been made magical, explore for more.</string>

    <string name="slide_3_title">Work study</string>
    <string name="slide_3_desc">You can now apply for work study in few minutes by just filling a digital form.</string>

    <string name="slide_4_title">Campus market</string>
    <string name="slide_4_desc">The pain of going off campus to buy everything is solved. Buy goods right on campus.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">LoginActivity</string>
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in or register</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="welcome">"Welcome !"</string>
    <string name="invalid_username">Not a valid username</string>
    <string name="invalid_password">Password must be >5 characters</string>
    <string name="Announcement" formatted="true">October 4. 2021\n\n

        Dear Student,\n\n

        The Lord has been good to our University community. Despite the challenges that descended upon us at the beginning of the pandemic, the semester has been successful.\n\n

Congratulations to all of you. For those who have few exams to complete, I wish you God\'s blessings on your efforts to excel in your exams.\n\n
        <b>Please take note of the following as you prepare for your vacation:\n\n
        1. All Resident students, except nursing whose semester ends on October 29, 2021, must vacate the halls by 5:O0 pm on Sunday, October 9, 2021.\n\n

 2. Vacate your room by properly going through the checking-out process with the Assistant Hall Deans.\n\n

 3. Ensure your room is clean. Occupants who fail to do so will be charged accordingly.\n\n

 4. Submit your key to the Assistant Hall Dean as you check out. Failure to do so will attract a fee equivalent to three times the cost of replacing the lock.\n\n

 5. International students wish to be residents on campus during vacation must apply for accommodation at the office of the Dean, Student Life and Services office before Sunday, October 9, 2021.\n\n

            6. Students who want to engage in the work-study program during the break should apply to the General Administration Department and for accomodation, at the office of the Dean, Student Life and Services office. <u>Remember that only those willing to work 8 hours a day during the vacation will be given accomodation on campus.</u></b>\n\n

For the safety of our campus community, please adhere to the above directives.\n\n

Once again, I wish you all the best and happy holidays.\n\n

Remember to stay blessed.\n\n

Martha Duah, PhD\n
Dean, Student Life and Service.\n</string>

    <string name="about">"The Valley View Studentlife mobile application was developed by Kio Godsfavour Ngo, a product of VVU. The mobile application was developed as part of his final year project when he discovered existing problems he had encountered during his four-year tenure as a student at the University.
        \n\nThe VVUSA strives to make the studentlife experience at Valley View University exponentially better by tackling 4 very key aspects that students encounter during their stay on campus:
        \n1. The four hostels
        \n2. The Cafeteria
        \n3. The Workstudy department
        \n4. Buying and selling on campus

        \n\nThe app performs four(4) primary functions:
        \n1. It gives students of the University the choice of booking rooms right from the comfort of their homes.
        \n2. It generates digital chits for students to feed from the cafeteria rather than the paper chits, which contributed to paper wastage at the University.
        \n3. It gives students an automated way of applying for workstudy positions.
        \n4. It creates a virtual market where students can buy and sell."</string>
    <string name="login_failed">"Login failed"</string>
    <string name="NoAnnouncement">No announcements yet!</string>


    <string name="meal_name">Cheese Burger</string>
    <string name="meal_description">
        A properly seasoned patty topped with a slice of fresh tomato, cheese and lettuce enclosed in a
        fluffy bun. It’s accompanied with a side of fries with a sweet and spicy dip.
    </string>
    <!-- Hardcoding the price is for demo purpose only.
    You shouldn't do this in prod -->
    <string name="meal_price">Pay &#x20A6;4,000</string>
    <string name="payment_prompt">Card details</string>
    <string name="card_number">Card Number</string>
    <string name="card_expiry">Card Expiry</string>
    <string name="card_cvv">CVV</string>
    <string name="payment">"https://paystack.com/pay/pan-h-renm"</string>

    <string-array name="option">
        <item>Products</item>
        <item>Services</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Gender">
        <item>Male</item>
        <item>Female</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="floor">
        <item>GF</item>
        <item>FF</item>
        <item>SF</item>
        <item>TF</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="block">
        <item>A</item>
        <item>B</item>
        <item>C</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="roomNumber">
        <item>1</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>3</item>
        <item>4</item>
        <item>5</item>
        <item>6</item>
        <item>7</item>
        <item>8</item>
        <item>9</item>
        <item>10</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="productCategories">
        <item>Clothes</item>
        <item>Shoes</item>
        <item>Bags</item>
        <item>Gadgets</item>
        <item>Cosmetics</item>
        <item>Stationary</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="serviceCategories">
        <item>Gadget Repairs</item>
        <item>Hair Dressing</item>
        <item>Barbering</item>
        <item>Catering</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="conditionSpinner">
        <item>Brand new</item>
        <item>Used</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>